paparazziaccessories.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy

## Introduction

Paparazzi Accessories LLC (referred to herein as “Paparazzi Accessories LLC” “we,” “us” and “our”) understands the importance of privacy of individuals (referred to as “users” and “you”). This privacy notice outlines the personal information Paparazzi Accessories LLC may collect and how Paparazzi Accessories LLC will use and disclose that information. Paparazzi Accessories LLC is committed to protecting your personal information. We have adopted the following policies with regard to collection and distribution of information.

## Information Collection

Paparazzi Accessories LLC may collect two different types of information, Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. “Personally Identifiable Information” (“PII”) is information that identifies you as an individual – for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, billing address and shipping information. “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” (“Non-PII”) is aggregated information, demographic information, IP addresses, user behavior data from web interaction metrics tools and any other information that does not reveal your specific identity.-

During the Independent Consultant enrollment process, or while purchasing product on Paparazzi Accessories LLC maintained websites, Paparazzi Accessories LLC may collect PII about you that may be considered sensitive.

Paparazzi Accessories LLC may also collect PII about you from, among other places: information you provide directly to us, information regarding the services that Paparazzi Accessories LLC currently provides or has previously provided to you, information Paparazzi Accessories LLC receives from our affiliated entities or third parties relating to the establishment of our relationship or the provision of services to you.

This information can be received in any manner, including in-person discussions, telephone conversations, and electronic or other written communications.

## Cookies

We may collect information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us to estimate our audience size and usage pattern, to store information about your preferences (and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests), to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to our site. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

## Information Use

Paparazzi Accessories LLC may collect PII about you to establish or maintain our relationship with you, respond to your inquiries, provide you with services you have requested, keep you informed of services we think may be of interest to you, personalize your experience with us, and other reasons.

Without PII, Paparazzi Accessories LLC may be unable to provide you with the services you have requested.

## Disclosure of Information

Paparazzi Accessories LLC does not sell or lease PII about you to others.

Paparazzi Accessories LLC may share PII about you with others as permitted by contractual agreement or as required by law, such as our affiliates, third parties in connection with the provision of services to you, government entities and regulatory bodies, and those with whom you have requested us to share information.

Unless restricted by law, regulation, contract or professional standards, Paparazzi Accessories LLC may transfer PII about you outside of the United States to other countries for the purposes described in this privacy notice.

Paparazzi Accessories LLC will not share PII about you with an unaffiliated third party who is not performing services for us without first obtaining your permission, except if such sharing is otherwise permitted by this privacy notice.

Paparazzi Accessories LLC will provide PII about you to the following types of third parties for the associated reasons:

**Carriers** : Paparazzi Accessories LLC will provide your name and address to companies which provide a delivery service between Paparazzi Accessories LLC and its customers as a means of delivering our products to you as quickly as possible.

**Financial Institutions** : Paparazzi Accessories LLC will provide financial institutions with your payment information, name, address, and phone number in order to process any orders placed by you and complete payment of the transaction to Paparazzi Accessories LLC.

**Logistics** : Paparazzi Accessories LLC will provide your name, address and phone number to those entities or people within our network of distribution in order to process and ship your orders with speed and accuracy.

Paparazzi Accessories LLC requires third parties who perform services for us to agree to treat PII about you confidentially and securely. Prior to collection your PII, any such third parties are required to sign a service agreement, which includes the privacy policy outlined here. Note that this statement does not address the privacy practices or polices of our Independent Consultants. However, Paparazzi Accessories LLC Independent Consultants agree, as specified in our Policies and Procedures, to comply with all applicable privacy laws and regulations.

Notwithstanding any other provision of this notice or the Terms and Conditions of Use to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose and use your PII if we believe that we are required to do so: (a) by law; (b) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena; (c) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request; (d) to enforce our other terms, conditions, or policies; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Paparazzi Accessories LLC , you or others; and/or (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages we may sustain. For example, we may to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose PII about you to law enforcement agencies to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities.

Because Non-PII does not personally identify you, we reserve the right to use Non-PII, and to disclose Non-PII to third parties, for any purpose.

## Access

You may request access to the PII that Paparazzi Accessories LLC has about you. You may also request the correction, amendment or deletion of PII about you that is inaccurate. Paparazzi Accessories LLC will treat requests for access, correction, amendment or deletion of PII about you in accordance with its internal policies and applicable legal requirements.

## Information Security and Integrity

Paparazzi Accessories LLC maintains reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to protect PII from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Our personnel and the personnel of our affiliates are provided access to PII about you only if they have a need to know the information in connection with a legitimate business purpose, such as (a) the provision of services to you or (b) to help identify other services that Paparazzi Accessories LLC and its affiliates offer that may be of interest or use to you.

Additionally, Paparazzi Accessories LLC will only use PII for the purpose which it was intentionally collected. Paparazzi Accessories LLC will take reasonable measures to safeguard your information and ensure that is accurate, complete and current.

## Enforcement

Paparazzi Accessories LLC takes a self-assessment approach to verify that we are within compliance of this policy. Paparazzi Accessories LLC employees are trained to adhere with this privacy policy and Paparazzi Accessories LLC administers discipline to those employees who do not comply.

## Changes to This Privacy Notice

Paparazzi Accessories LLC reserves the right to change this privacy notice. Any changes to this notice will become effective upon posting of the revised notice on the Internet or as required by law.
